const JavaScriptQuestions =[

    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(10 / 2);`?",
        correctAnswer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(10 % 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(5.0 / 2);`?",
        correctAnswer: "2.5"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(-10 / 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "-3"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(10 + 2 * 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "16"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(10 - 2 * 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(10 / 0);`?",
        correctAnswer: "Infinity"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(2 < 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(3 == 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(2 != 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(3 > 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "false"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(typeof 10);`?",
        correctAnswer: "number"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(typeof 'hello');`?",
        correctAnswer: "string"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(typeof true);`?",
        correctAnswer: "boolean"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(typeof null);`?",
        correctAnswer: "object"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(typeof undefined);`?",
        correctAnswer: "undefined"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(3 * 4 / 2);`?",
        correctAnswer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(2 * (3 + 4));`?",
        correctAnswer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(3 + 4 * 2);`?",
        correctAnswer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `let i = 3, j = 4; console.log(++i + ++j);`?",
        correctAnswer: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `let i = 7, j = 2; console.log(--i - --j);`?",
        correctAnswer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(3.14 + 2.71);`?",
        correctAnswer: "5.85"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log((5 > 3) && (2 < 4));`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log((5 > 3) || (2 > 4));`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(!(2 == 2));`?",
        correctAnswer: "false"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(2 & 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(2 | 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(2 ^ 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(sizeof(short));`?",
        correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(sizeof(double));`?",
        correctAnswer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(sizeof(char));`?",
        correctAnswer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(sizeof(long long));`?",
        correctAnswer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(5 & 2);`?",
        correctAnswer: "0"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(5 | 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(5 ^ 1);`?",
        correctAnswer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(3 << 1);`?",
        correctAnswer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(3 >> 1);`?",
        correctAnswer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(10 / 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(10 % 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(-10 % 3);`?",
        correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(1 && 1);`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(1 && 0);`?",
        correctAnswer: "false"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(1 || 0);`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(1 || 1);`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(!0);`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(!1);`?",
        correctAnswer: "false"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log((3 > 2) && (4 > 3));`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log((3 < 2) || (4 > 3));`?",
        correctAnswer: "true"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log((3 < 2) && (4 < 3));`?",
        correctAnswer: "false"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(5 / 2);`?",
        correctAnswer: "2.5"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of `console.log(5 / 2);`?",
        correctAnswer: "2"
    },

];
export default JavaScriptQuestions;